energyactioncoalition.org 2018-05-06

# Privacy Policy | Power Shift Network

**The Power Shift Network has a firm commitment to protecting your online privacy.**

We have created this privacy notice to explain how we use information that you may provide while visiting websites operated by the Power Shift Network, and to demonstrate our firm commitment to Internet privacy. We may modify this policy from time to time, so we encourage you to check this page when revisiting this website.

#### The Information We Collect

The only information we collect from a normal web site visit is the name of your internet service provider, the browser and type of machine you are using, the web site that referred you to us, the pages you request and the date and time you request them. We use this information to generate statistics and measure site activity in order to improve the quality of our site to our visitors.

Like most websites, Power Shift Network may place a “cookie,” or small file, in the browser files of a visitor’s computer. We use cookies to save information you give us so that you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. This allows us to personalize the site to your taste and provide the best web experience possible to our visitors.

We do encourage you to voluntarily share your email address and other information with us, because we can’t build the movement we need to win the fight for climate justice without you! 

 _Note:_ The Power Shift Network's websites, including [PowerShift.org](http://www.powershift.org/) and [PowerShift2016.org](http://www.powershift2016.org/), are not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

#### How We Use Your Information

 **Power Shift Network will not use your personal information for any purpose other than that for which it is submitted.**

We use personal information collected in connection with registration for an event or program to manage event participation, reply to inquiries and process billing and will only share personal information with the contractors and/or partners responsible for organizing/sponsoring the event or program you are registering to attend. We will also add your name to our mailing list, so you can engage in future events and campaigns. If you do not want to receive any further communications from us, you can always unsubscribe via the link at the bottom of any email we send.

If you sign up to receive email or SMS updates from the Power Shift Network, we commit to providing you with accurate and timely information about our campaign activities. While the vast majority of communications will come to you directly from Power Shift Network, some information on our lists, such as your name and address, may be provided to trusted Power Shift Network allies from time to time. These allies may, for example, be organizing related events in your community.

You may opt out of email communication from the Power Shift Network at any time via the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email we send. You may opt out of SMS communication at any point by texting STOP to 228466.

#### How We Protect Your Privacy

Power Shift Network makes every effort to ensure the secure collection and transmission of sensitive user information using industry standard data collection and encryption methodologies. Permission to access your information is granted only to you and Power Shift Network employees or contractors who need to know that information to provide services to you.

If you choose to make a donation to Power Shift Network or otherwise provide us your credit card information (including in connection with registration for events or programs), your credit card information will be used only for the transaction for which it is submitted through our secure online payment system. **We do not retain credit card information or transmit credit card information to anyone else. We will never  sell or otherwise disclose such information.**

 _Note:_ Although we make every possible effort to store information collected by this website in a secure operating environment, we cannot guarantee complete security.
